<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearA.label>Underwear (half elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearA.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearA.description>Normal underwear made of leather or cloth.</AS_WHE_UnderwearA.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearB.label>Pink frilly underwear (half elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearB.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearB.description>Underwear made of leather or cloth. It has frills and a cute finish. Rumor has it that wearing it on an important day brings good luck to the wearer.</AS_WHE_UnderwearB.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearC.label>Blue frilly underwear (half elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearC.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearC.description>Underwear made of leather or cloth. It has frills and a cute finish. Rumor has it that wearing it on an important day brings good luck to the wearer.</AS_WHE_UnderwearC.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearD.label>Sexy underwear (half elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearD.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearD.description>Sexy underwear made of leather or cloth. The design makes the other party's heart jump, and the more inexperienced the opponent is, the more they forget their composure. We will surely be filled with happiness together.</AS_WHE_UnderwearD.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearE.label>Smart Underwear (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearE.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearE.description>Underwear made of leather or cloth? The design is a work of deep craftsmanship that even words can no longer be used to describe. Your partner will be satisfied with its charm and will be tied with a stronger bond.</AS_WHE_UnderwearE.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearF.label>Baby Doll (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearF.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearF.description>A sexy baby doll. Its design allows you to see through various parts while protecting important parts, making it ideal for night battles.</AS_WHE_UnderwearF.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearG.label>White Baby Doll (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearG.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearG.description>A high-class baby doll based on white. Not only is it an elegant design, but it is also a first-class product that is studded with sexiness to highlight the charm of women.</AS_WHE_UnderwearG.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearH.label>Black Baby Doll (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearH.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearH.description>A high-class baby doll based on black. Not only is it an elegant design, but it is also a first-class product that is studded with sexiness to highlight the charm of women.</AS_WHE_UnderwearH.description>

  <AS_WHE_UnderwearI.label>Luxury Baby Doll (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_UnderwearI.label>
  <AS_WHE_UnderwearI.description>A luxury baby doll. Not only is it an elegant design, but it is also a first-class product that is studded with sexiness to highlight the charm of women.</AS_WHE_UnderwearI.description>

  <AS_WHE_Neeso.label>Knee Socks (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_Neeso.label>
  <AS_WHE_Neeso.description>Knee socks made of leather or cloth.</AS_WHE_Neeso.description>

  <AS_WHE_StripeNeeso.label>Stripe Knee Socks (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_StripeNeeso.label>
  <AS_WHE_StripeNeeso.description>High quality striped knee socks made of leather or cloth.</AS_WHE_StripeNeeso.description>

  <AS_WHE_GarterBelt.label>Garter Belt (Half Elf)</AS_WHE_GarterBelt.label>
  <AS_WHE_GarterBelt.description>A garter belt. A single belt running over a beautiful body will maximize the attractiveness of the wearer.</AS_WHE_GarterBelt.description>

</LanguageData>